

# Lisa Hurman

# STUDENT



lisahuurm@gmail.com 6 06 37467427





### **ABOUT ME**

I am a highly motivated student with a passion for creative technology. I enjoy designing and developing with focus on accessibility and the user experience. I am an agile and flexible programmer and have experience in multiple programming languages and all fases of the development process.

# **EDUCATION**

### Creative Media and Game Technologies Bachelor, Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences September 2019 - Present

At my current study I am learning the ins and outs of coding and software design and development.

#### Game Design and Development Minor, Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences

September 2022 - February 2023

At my minor I functioned in a team simulating an independent game studio as developer and producer. I learned a lot about team management, game development and the full software production process.

#### Havo, Herbert Vissers College, Nieuw-Vennep

2013 - 2018

### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Frontend Webdeveloper Internship, Minty Media, Haarlem

August 2021 - January 2022

As frontend developer at my internship I made designs with AdobeXD and worked with WordPress, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP to create websites and webshops. I had close contact with our customers to receive assignments and apply feedback directly.

#### Private Tutor, StudentsPlus, Hoofddorp

September 2020 - Present

As tutor I work freelance to assist students with any difficulties they might have which helps me develop my communication and time management skills.

## Peercoach, Rotterdam University of Applied Sciences

September 2020 - July 2021

As peercoach I worked for my study to assist other students and I was involved with event management, teaching and tutoring.

#### **SKILLS**

Webdevelopment	Game development	Design
HTML 🖈	Unreal Engine 🖈	User Experience
CSS 🖈	C++ <b>★</b>	Accessibility 🖈
JavaScript 🖈	Unity	AdobeXD 🖈
React.js	C#	Photoshop
Typescript	Blueprinting 🖈	

# LANGUAGE

I was raised bilingual and I am fluent in both **English** and **Dutch**.

## LINKS

Portfolio Website LinkedIn